Guide to the Greenwall Foundation Archive 1976-2011 (bulk 1991-2010) MSS 336
© 2012 Fales Library and Special Collections
Greenwall Foundation Archive
Bulk, 1991-2010
1976-2011
MSS 336
© 2012 Fales Library and Special Collections
47.5 linear feet (38 boxes)
The Greenwall Foundation’s Arts and Humanities Program (1991-2011) supported arts organizations and emerging artists. This collection contains subject files of artists and organizations who applied for and/or received grants from the Greenwall Foundation. It also contains audiovisual media and objects that were the products of Greenwall grants.
The Greenwall Foundation.
Arrangement
The Greenwall Foundation Archive is arranged into three series:
Series I: Subject Files
Series II: Media
Series III: Objects
The material within each series is arranged alphabetically.
Conditions Governing Access
Open to researchers. Appointments are necessary for the use of manuscript and archival collections.
Scope and Content
This collection contains the records of the Greenwall Foundation's Arts and Humanities Program. It consists largely of files on the artists and organizations who received funding from the foundation, which include financial records, updates on projects, clippings, and correspondence, as well as audiovisual media and objects sent to Greenwall by the artists.
Historical Note
The Greenwall Foundation was founded in 1949 by Frank and Anna Greenwall, in memory of their daughter, Susan, who had died of bone cancer at age 16. Their original mission was to provide grants and fellowships for students, and to help fund medical research on children’s diseases. Throughout the years, the foundation grew and began supporting more diverse interests. In 1991, the Greenwall Foundation’s Arts and Humanities Program was founded, with the mission to “Support emerging artists…, promote artistic experimentation…, enhance the international exposure of New York City artists…, and respond to opportunities provided by exceptional situations.”
The Arts and Humanities program was intended to support “innovation and creativity in the visual, performing and literary arts” and was “interested in encouraging emerging artists and the development of new artistic works”. This focus on emerging artists and new works set the Greenwall Foundation apart from more traditional funding agencies. In addition to the Foundation’s one year grants, it also offered three year grants. These one-time multiyear awards were given to arts organizations, to expand and improve their administrative and structural foundations, allowing them to grow and addressing their needs in the long term. The foundation also offered the Oscar M. Ruebenhausen Commission, which endorsed and sponsored an artist who showed expertise in the annually changing discipline chosen by the foundation’s board.
The Greenwall Foundation concluded its arts and humanities program in 2011. During the twenty years that the Foundation was funding the arts, more than 1200 grants were given out to artists in various disciplines. The Foundation now solely focuses on the Greenwall Faculty Scholars Program in Bioethics.
Separated Materials
Books and other print publications were separated from the collection. Duplicates were deaccessioned, and other material will be cataloged in Bobcat. A list of separated materials is available.
The Greenwall Foundation.; Art patronage.; Artists |z United States.; Grant proposals.; Modern dance.; Non-profit artists centers.; Opera.
- Series I: Subject Files
  Scope and Content
  This series contains the files kept by the Greenwall Foundation, with information about, contracts with, and material submitted by the artists and organizations who receieved funding from the Foundation.
  - Aaron Davis Hall, 1995-2000 (Box 1, Folder 1-3)
  - Abacus Parts, 1999-2000 (Box 1, Folder 4-5)
  - Abigail Adams Smith Museum, 1990-1992 (Box 1, Folder 6-7)
  - Abington Theatre Company (The Berrilla Kerr Next Step Workshop Program), 2000-2002 (Box 1, Folder 8-10)
  - Abrons Arts Center (Underground at the Abrons), 2008-2010 (Box 1, Folder 11-13)
  - Academy of American Poets, 1997-2000 (Box 1, Folder 14-16)
  - Accra Shepp - "Atlas", 1995 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Acting Company, 1991-1996 (Box 1, Folder 18-19)
  - Adobe Theatre Company, 1998-2004 (Box 1, Folder 20-24)
  - Alvin Ailey Dance, 1987-1996 (Box 1, Folder 25-26)
  - American Academy of Child & Adolescent Phychiatry (Hamburg), 1996-1997 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - American Academy of Dramatic Arts, 1987-1989 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - American Ballet Theatre, 1988-2000 (Box 1, Folder 29-30)
  - American Composers Forum, 1999-2000 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - American Composers Orchestra, Inc, 1990-2010 (Box 1, Folder 32-38)
  - American Contemporary Music Ensemble (ACME), 2008-2009 (Box 1, Folder 39-40)
  - American Music Center, 2006-2007 (Box 1, Folder 41-42)
  - American Opera Projects, Inc, 1992-2004 (Box 1, Folder 43-48)
  - American Place Theater, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - American Tap Dance Orchestra, 1991-1994 (Box 2, Folder 2-3)
  - Amiel Malale Dance, 1994-1996 (Box 2, Folder 4-6)
  - Anita Saewitz, 1994-2000 (Box 2, Folder 7-8)
  - Annie B. Parson - Big Dance Theater, 1997-2005 (Box 2, Folder 9-12)
  - Anthony De Mare, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Architectural League of New York, 1994-2000 (Box 2, Folder 14-18)
  - Arden Party, 1995-1997 (Box 2, Folder 19-20)
  - Art in General, 1997-2010 (Box 2, Folder 21-28)
  - ART/NY, 1990-1999 (Box 2, Folder 29-30)
  - Art Container, 2001-2002 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Artists Alliance Inc, 2005-2010 (Box 2, Folder 32-36)
  - Artists Space, 1991-2006 (Box 3, Folder 1-5)
  - ArtsConnection, 1987-1988 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Arts at St. Ann's, 2000-2005 (Box 3, Folder 7-10)
  - Arts Forward Fund, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 11-12)
  - Asia Society, 1983-2009 (Box 3, Folder 13-16)
  - Asian American Writers Workshop, 1993-1997 (Box 3, Folder 17-19)
  - Atlantic Theater Company, 1992-2002 (Box 3, Folder 20-25)
  - Ballet Hispanico of New York, 1999-2001 (Box 3, Folder 26-27)
  - Ballet Tech, 1999-2001 (Box 3, Folder 28-29)
  - BAM (Brooklyn Academy of Music), 1987-2001 (Box 3, Folder 30-38)
  - Banana Bag and Bodice, 2008 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Bang on a Can, 1991-2009 (Box 4, Folder 2-9)
  - Bargemusic, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Barrow Group, The, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Battleworks Dance Company, 2007-2008 (Box 4, Folder 12-13)
  - Bebe Miller Company, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Big Apple Circus, 1986-1991 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Big Art Group, 2003-2006 (Box 4, Folder 16-17)
  - Bill Young & Dancers, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Blue Heron Arts Center, 2000-2001 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Brian Brooks Moving Company, 2004-2010 (Box 4, Folder 20-23)
  - Bronx Arts Ensemble, 1992-1997 (Box 4, Folder 24-26)
  - Bronx Council on the Arts, 1992-2002 (Box 4, Folder 27-32)
  - Bronx Museum of the Arts, 1987-2010 (Box 4, Folder 33-40)
  - Brooklyn Arts Exchange, 2009 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Brooklyn College Conservatory of Music, 1987-1989 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Brooklyn Historical Society, 1988-2009 (Box 5, Folder 1-2)
  - Brooklyn Museum of Art, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Brooklyn Museum - Computer systems, 1987-1989 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Brooklyn Philharmonic Orchestra, 2000-2007 (Box 5, Folder 5-9)
  - Brooklyn Public Library Foundation, 2001-2005 (Box 5, Folder 10-15)
  - Buglisi / Foreman Dance, 1995-1997 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Builders Association, The (Marianne Weems), 1995-2005 (Box 5, Folder 17-24)
  - Cabinet Magazine, 2003-2010 (Box 5, Folder 25-29)
  - Cave Canem, 2001-2010 (Box 5, Folder 30-36)
  - Celebrate Brooklyn!, 1992-2000 (Box 6, Folder 1-5)
  - Center for Contemporary Opera, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Chamber Music Society of Lincoln Center, 1987-2002 (Box 6, Folder 7-11)
  - ChameckiLerner, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Channel 13 (WNET), 1976-1985 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Chashama, 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Cherry Lane Alternative, Inc (Cherry Lane Theatre), 1999-2004 (Box 6, Folder 15-19)
  - Chinatown History Museum, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Chocolate Factory, The, 2008-2010 (Box 6, Folder 21-23)
  - Christopher Williams, 2006-2010 (Box 6, Folder 24-27)
  - Circle Repertory Company, 1991-1994 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Circum Arts - "Dance at Miller", 1995 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - City Lore, 1994-2000 (Box 6, Folder 30-32)
  - Civilians, The, 2002-2010 (Box 6, Folder 33-37)
  - Classic Stage Company (CSC Repertory), 1988-2001 (Box 6, Folder 38-43)
  - Classical Theatre of Harlem, The, 2004-2006 (Box 6, Folder 44-45)
  - Clove Galilee / Jenny Rogers, 2004 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Clubbed Thumb, 2003-2010 (Box 7, Folder 2-7)
  - Collision Theory, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 8-9)
  - CoDanceCo, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Composers Collaborative, 2000-2002 (Box 7, Folder 11-13)
  - Composers Recording Inc., 1994-1997 (Box 7, Folder 14-15)
  - Concert Artists Guild, Inc., 1989-2007 (Box 7, Folder 16-17)
  - Concordia, 1989-1992 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Conjunction Arts, 2001-2007 (Box 7, Folder 19-20)
  - CorbinDances (NYFA), 2006 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Council of Literary Magazines & Presses, 2004 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Creative Time, 1990-2006 (Box 7, Folder 23-30)
  - Crossing Jamaica Avenue, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Cucaracha Theatre, 1992-1998 (Box 7, Folder 32-35)
  - Cue Art Foundation, 2006-2010 (Box 8, Folder 1-4)
  - Culture Project, The, 1992-2005 (Box 8, Folder 5-6)
  - Dan Hurlin - "The Shoulder", 1996-1997 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Dance and Be Still Arts, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Dance & Film, 1994-1997 (Box 8, Folder 9-11)
  - Dance Kumikokimoto, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Dance Theatre of Harlem, 1993-1994 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Dance Theater Workshop, 1988-2010 (Box 8, Folder 14-24)
  - Dancing in the Streets, 1989-2005 (Box 8, Folder 25-32)
  - Danspace Project, 1991-2007 (Box 8, Folder 33-39)
  - David Dorfman Dance (Dance Continuum), 1990-1997 (Box 8, Folder 40-41)
  - David Parker Dance, 2003 (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - David Rousseve / Reality, 1992-1995 (Box 8, Folder 43-44)
  - Dean Moss, 1995-2000 (Box 9, Folder 1-3)
  - Debate Society, The, 2007-2010 (Box 9, Folder 4-6)
  - Dieu Donne Papermill, Inc., 1991-2011 (Box 9, Folder 7-16)
  - Dixon Place, 1990-2009 (Box 9, Folder 17-24)
  - Donna Uchizono Company, 2001-2003 (Box 9, Folder 25-27)
  - Doug Elkins Dance Company, 1994-1995 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Drama Dept, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Drama League of New York, 1992-1996 (Box 9, Folder 30-32)
  - Drawing Center, The, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Drawing Center, The, 1991-2005 (Box 10, Folder 1-6)
  - d.u.m.b.o. arts center, 2008 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Dusan Tynek Dance Theatre`, 2009-2010 (Box 10, Folder 8-9)
  - Ear/Say, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Edge Theater Company, 2005-2006 (Box 10, Folder 11-12)
  - eighth blackbird (NYFA), 2002 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Eiko & Koma, 1990-1993 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Elaine Kaufman Cultural Center, 1996-2010 (Box 10, Folder 15-22)
  - Elevator Repair Service, 2007-2011 (Box 10, Folder 23-25)
  - Elevator Repair Service, 1999-2004 (Box 11, Folder 1-5)
  - Eliza Miller Dance Company, 2001-2003 (Box 11, Folder 6-8)
  - En Garde Arts, 1990-1997 (Box 11, Folder 9-12)
  - Ensemble Studio Theatre, 1988-2002 (Box 11, Folder 13-17)
  - EOS, 1998-2001 (Box 11, Folder 18-20)
  - Equity Library Theatre, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Erik S. Guzman, 2008 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Ernesto Klar, 2009 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Essential Music, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Esopus Foundation, Ltd., The, 2004-2011 (Box 11, Folder 25-31)
  - Ethel's Foundation for the Arts, 2003-2010 (Box 11, Folder 32-37)
  - Exit Art, 2001-2006 (Box 11, Folder 38-42)
  - Exit Art, 1992-2000 (Box 12, Folder 1-5)
  - Eye on Dance: Video Restoration Project, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Eyebeam Atelier, 2002-2004 (Box 12, Folder 7-9)
  - Faye Driscoll, 2010 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Festival Chamber Music, 2005-2007 (Box 12, Folder 11-13)
  - Field, The (The Performance Zone), 1991-2011 (Box 12, Folder 14-16)
  - Figment (Action Arts League, Inc.), 2009 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Film/Video Arts, 1991-1997 (Box 12, Folder 18-19)
  - Five Myles, 2003-2010 (Box 12, Folder 20-24)
  - Flux Factory, 2005-2006 (Box 12, Folder 25-26)
  - Flying Machine Theater, The, 2001-2005 (Box 12, Folder 27-31)
  - Foundry Theatre Inc., The, 1994-2011 (Box 12, Folder 32-42)
  - Foxy Films, 2009-2010 (Box 13, Folder 1-2)
  - Fractured Atlas, 2009-2011 (Box 13, Folder 3-4)
  - Franklin Furnace, 1991-2005 (Box 13, Folder 5-7)
  - French Institute, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Friends of the Highline, 2010 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Gale Gates et al., 1999-2003 (Box 13, Folder 10-11)
  - Gallery Association of NYS, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Gamelan Son of Lion, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Gertrude Stein Rep, 1998-2000 (Box 13, Folder 14-15)
  - Given Fish, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Goliard Concerts, 1992-2000 (Box 13, Folder 17-18)
  - Gotham Arts Exchange, 2011 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Gowanus Arts Exchange, 1995-1997 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Gravity Hill Films, 2003 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Great Small Works, 1996-2001 (Box 13, Folder 22-25)
  - Greenwall Foundation - internal records, 1992-2010 (Box 13, Folder 26-31)
  - Harlem School of the Arts, 1984-1990 (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Harvestworks, 1994-2009 (Box 13, Folder 33-39)
  - HERE Arts Center, 2009-2011 (Box 13, Folder 40-42)
  - HERE Arts Center, 1994-2008 (Box 14, Folder 1-9)
  - Hoff-Barthelson Music School, 1999-2011 (Box 14, Folder 10-11)
  - Home for Contemporary Theatre and Art, 1990-1994 (Box 14, Folder 12-14)
  - Horizons Concerts, 1985-1989 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Hotchkiss School, The, 1996-2002 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Hourglass Group, 2003-2007 (Box 14, Folder 17-20)
  - Ice Theatre of New York, 1996 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Insignia Films, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - INTAR Hispanic American Arts Center, 1990-2008 (Box 14, Folder 23-28)
  - International Center for Photography, 2000-2001 (Box 14, Folder 29-30)
  - International Contemporary Ensemble, 2010-2011 (Box 14, Folder 31-32)
  - International Festival of Puppet Theatre, 1996-2001 (Box 14, Folder 33-35)
  - International Print Center New York, 2006-2008 (Box 14, Folder 36-38)
  - Inverse Theater, 1999-2001 (Box 14, Folder 39-40)
  - ISSUE Project Room, 2009-2010 (Box 15, Folder 1-2)
  - Issues TV, Ltd., 1999 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - J. Mandle Performance, 1999-2002 (Box 15, Folder 4-5)
  - Jamaica Arts Center, 1995-2010 (Box 15, Folder 6-8)
  - Jazz Gallery, The (Jazz at Lincoln Center), 1990-2010 (Box 15, Folder 9-15)
  - Joffrey Ballet, The, 1987-1995 (Box 15, Folder 16-19)
  - Johannes Wieland, 2004-2006 (Box 15, Folder 20-22)
  - John Jasperse Company, 2000-2002 (Box 15, Folder 23-25)
  - John Kelly, 1991-1993 (Box 15, Folder 26-28)
  - Jose Limon Dance Foundation, Inc., 1990-2003 (Box 15, Folder 29-33)
  - Joslin Diabetes Center, 1997-1999 (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - Joyce Theater Foundation, The, 1990-2006 (Box 15, Folder 35-41)
  - Juggernaut Theatre Company, 2008 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Jupiter Symphony, 1989-1990 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Justine Cooper (Lower Manhattan Cultural Council), 2009 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Kate Weare Company, 2007-2010 (Box 16, Folder 4-7)
  - Keigwin + Company, 2005-2010 (Box 16, Folder 8-11)
  - Kitchen, The, 1989-2011 (Box 16, Folder 12-22)
  - Kyle DeCamp, 1997-1998 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - La Mama, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - LAByrinth Theater Company, 2003 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Lark Theatre Company, The, 2006-2010 (Box 16, Folder 26-29)
  - Laura Peterson, 2009-2010 (Box 16, Folder 30-31)
  - LeeSaar the Company, 2008-2010 (Box 16, Folder 32-34)
  - LEMUR, 2004-2008 (Box 16, Folder 35-37)
  - Les Freres Corbusier, 2005 (Box 16, Folder 38)
  - Lincoln Center Theater, 1987-2000 (Box 16, Folder 39-43)
  - Lionheart, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Living Archives, 1994 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Lone Wolf Trive, 2006-2008 (Box 17, Folder 3-4)
  - Lower East Side Printshop, Inc, 2004-2010 (Box 17, Folder 5-8)
  - Lower East Side Tenement Museum, 1992-2009 (Box 17, Folder 9-13)
  - Lower Manhattan Cultural Council, 1997-2010 (Box 17, Folder 14-22)
  - Lynn Shapiro Dance Company, 1997-1998 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - MA-YI Theater Ensemble, Inc, 2003-2010 (Box 17, Folder 24-27)
  - Mabou Mines, 1994-2004 (Box 17, Folder 28-33)
  - Mad Alex (Arts Foundation), 1996-2001 (Box 17, Folder 34-39)
  - Manhattan Art Project (M.A.P.), 1996 (Box 17, Folder 40)
  - Manhattan Class Company, 1989-2002 (Box 18, Folder 1-5)
  - Manhattan College, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Manhattan School of Music, 1982-1994 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Manhattan Theatre Club, 1991-2000 (Box 18, Folder 8-11)
  - Mark Dendy Dance, 1999-2000 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Mark Taylor & Friends (Sartorius Dance, Inc.), 1989-1992 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Martha Graham Dance Company, 1994-1998 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Matthew Geller, 2001 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Maureen Fleming Dance, 1997-2003 (Box 18, Folder 16-17)
  - Media Alliance, 1994-1996 (Box 18, Folder 18-19)
  - Media Ties, 1997-2001 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Meet the Composer, 1989-1998 (Box 18, Folder 21-25)
  - Melissa Hacker, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Metropolitan Opera Association, 1985-1995 (Box 18, Folder 27-30)
  - Miller Theatre, 1999-2006 (Box 18, Folder 31-36)
  - Minetta Brook, 1996-2001 (Box 18, Folder 37-38)
  - Mirror Repertory Company, 1987-1989 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Momenta Inc. / Momenta Art, 1999-2010 (Box 19, Folder 2-9)
  - Monica Bill Barnes, 2004-2006 (Box 19, Folder 10-12)
  - Morris Jumel Mansion, 1991-1995 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Mosaic, 1996-1997 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Movement Research, 1991-2002 (Box 19, Folder 15-17)
  - Muhlenberg Hospital Foundation, 1991 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Muna Tseng Dance Projects, 1995-1997 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Museo del Barrio, El, 1988-2010 (Box 19, Folder 20-27)
  - Museum of Arts & Design, 2006-2008 (Box 20, Folder 1-2)
  - Museum of the City of New York, 1988-1992 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Museum of Modern Art, 1991-1994 (Box 20, Folder 4-5)
  - Museum of the Moving Image, 1995-2009 (Box 20, Folder 6-7)
  - Music at the Anthology, 1998-2009 (Box 20, Folder 8-15)
  - Music-Theatre Group, 1988-2001 (Box 20, Folder 16-19)
  - Musica Sacra, 1985-1991 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Nadja Press (NYFA), 1997 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Naked Angels, 1995-1998 (Box 20, Folder 22-23)
  - National Center for State Courts, 1995 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - National Orchestral Association, 1990-1992 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - National Theater of the USA, 2004-2008 (Box 20, Folder 26-28)
  - Neta Pulvermacher & Dancers, 1995-1997 (Box 20, Folder 29-30)
  - Network of Cultural Centers of Color, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - New Dramatists, 1993-2004 (Box 20, Folder 32-35)
  - New Georges, 2002-2010 (Box 21, Folder 1-6)
  - New Group, The, 1997-2000 (Box 21, Folder 7-9)
  - New Museum of Contemporary Art, 1991-2008 (Box 21, Folder 10-13)
  - New Press, The, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - New Radio and Performing Arts, 1997-2005 (Box 21, Folder 15-22)
  - New School for Social Research, 1989-1992 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - New School University, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - New Theatre of Brooklyn, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - New York Art Ensemble, 2007-2010 (Box 21, Folder 26-29)
  - New York Ballet, 1988-1996 (Box 21, Folder 30-34)
  - New York City Opera, 1984-2001 (Box 21, Folder 35-40)
  - New York City Players, 2003-2010 (Box 21, Folder 41-43)
  - New York City Players, 2001-2002 (Box 22, Folder 1-2)
  - New York Consortium for New Music, 1992-1998 (Box 22, Folder 3-5)
  - New York Council for the Humanities, 1991-1999 (Box 22, Folder 6-7)
  - New York Experimental Glass Workshop, 1991-1994 (Box 22, Folder 8-9)
  - New York Festival of Song, 1992-1996 (Box 22, Folder 10-11)
  - New York Firefighters 9-11 Disaster Relief Fund, 2001 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - New York Foundation for the Arts, 1990-2011 (Box 22, Folder 13-18)
  - New York Historical Society, 1991-1993 (Box 22, Folder 19-20)
  - New York Landmarks Conservancy, 1991-1997 (Box 22, Folder 21-23)
  - New York Medical College, 2001-2003 (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - New York Philharmonic, 1992-1995 (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - New York Public Library, 1988-1996 (Box 22, Folder 26-28)
  - New York Theatre Workshop, 1989-2001 (Box 22, Folder 29-33)
  - New York University - OMR Commission, 1997-2008 (Box 22, Folder 34)
  - New York Youth Symphony, 1986-2000 (Box 22, Folder 35-39)
  - Nicholas Leichter Dance, 2001-2003 (Box 23, Folder 1-3)
  - Nin Bruderman (NYFA), 2006 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Ninety-Second Street Y (92nd St. Y), 1990-2002 (Box 23, Folder 5-10)
  - NurtureArt, 2008-2010 (Box 23, Folder 11-13)
  - Nuyorican Poets Cafe, 1994-1995 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Obies & Bessies, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - O'Day Dance, 1997 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Old Merchant's House, 1991-1993 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Only Tribe, The, 2008 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Ontological-Hysteric Theatre, Inc, 1999-2009 (Box 23, Folder 19-24)
  - Opelika Pictures, 1995-1999 (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - Open City Magazine & Books, 2002-2004 (Box 23, Folder 26-27)
  - Opera at the Academy, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 28)
  - Opera Ebony, 1997-2000 (Box 23, Folder 29-30)
  - Opera Ensemble of New York, 1986-1990 (Box 23, Folder 31)
  - Orpheus Chamber Orchestra, 1995 (Box 23, Folder 32)
  - Oscar M. Ruebhausen Award and Commission, 1999-2009 (Box 23, Folder 33-36)
  - Out of the Shadows, 1994 (Box 23, Folder 37)
  - Page Seventy-Three Productions, 2006-2010 (Box 24, Folder 1-4)
  - Palissimo, 2008-2010 (Box 24, Folder 5-7)
  - Pan Asian Repertory Theatre, 1988-1994 (Box 24, Folder 8-9)
  - Parnassus Contemporary Music Ensemble, 1988-1990 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Parsons Dance Foundation, 1991-1992 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Pascal Rioult Dance, 1998-2000 (Box 24, Folder 12-13)
  - Past Present, The, 1999 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Paul Taylor Dance Company, 1989-1991 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Pearl Theatre Dance Company, 1991-2001 (Box 24, Folder 16-19)
  - Pentacle / Danceworks, 1990-2004 (Box 24, Folder 20-23)
  - Pepatian, 1992-1995 (Box 24, Folder 24-25)
  - Performa, 2007 (Box 24, Folder 26)
  - Performance Space 122, Inc. (P.S. 122), 2006-2011 (Box 24, Folder 27-32)
  - Performance Space 122, Inc. (P.S. 122), 1990-2003 (Box 25, Folder 1-5)
  - Peter Pucci Plus Dancers, 1991-1995 (Box 25, Folder 6-8)
  - Pick Up Performance Company, 1990-2000 (Box 25, Folder 9-14)
  - Pierpont Morgan Library, 1987-1990 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Playwrights Horizons, 1989-2001 (Box 25, Folder 16-19)
  - Poetry Calendar, 1995-1998 (Box 25, Folder 20-22)
  - Poetry Project, The, 1995-2000 (Box 25, Folder 23-25)
  - Poetry Society of America, 1991-2011 (Box 25, Folder 26-33)
  - Poets House, 1991-2005 (Box 26, Folder 1-9)
  - Poets and Writers, 1990-1993 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Pratt Institute, 2000 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Present Company, The, 2001 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Primary Stages, 1994-2000 (Box 26, Folder 13-16)
  - Printed Matter, 1996-1997 (Box 26, Folder 17-18)
  - Project Ballet, 2001-2002 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - P.S. 1 Contemporary Art Center, 1991-1999 (Box 26, Folder 20-22)
  - Public Art Fund, 1997-2003 (Box 26, Folder 23-29)
  - Public Theatre, The, 1988-1999 (Box 26, Folder 30-35)
  - Queens Library Foundation, 1994 (Box 26, Folder 36)
  - Queens Museum of Art, 2005-2010 (Box 26, Folder 37-40)
  - Queens Museum of Art, 1991-2004 (Box 27, Folder 1-5)
  - Queens Symphony Orchestra, 1992-2002 (Box 27, Folder 6-9)
  - Queens Theatre in the Park, 2004-2010 (Box 27, Folder 10-15)
  - Ralph Lemon Company, 1992-1995 (Box 27, Folder 16-17)
  - Rattlestick Playwrights Theater, 2004-2006 (Box 27, Folder 18-20)
  - Red Dive, 2002 (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - Reduta Deux, 2001 (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - Reggie Wilson / Fist and Heel, 2002-2005 (Box 27, Folder 23-24)
  - Regina Nejman, 2006-2007 (Box 27, Folder 25-26)
  - Repertorio Espanol, 1989-2000 (Box 27, Folder 27-32)
  - Rhizome.org, 2003-2010 (Box 27, Folder 33-37)